fxprotrade.com 2016-06-21

# Privacy Policy Security Privacy Policy Security

FX ProTrade respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients as well as our current clients.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you progressing to FX ProTrade and request to open an investment portfolio or a live account or demo account as an essential step to learn Forex, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing client service. Such information may include:

 **Application Information** \- Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, contact info, mailing address, birth date, occupation, assets, and income.

 **Transaction Information** \- Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries and our responses.

 **Verification Information** \- Information necessary to verify your identity such as a passport or drivers license.

  * FX ProTrade does not disclose any information about you or your transaction Information, or account information, there is no third party except through you.
  * FX ProTrade may enter into cooperation agreements with non-affiliated third parties to improve the customer services and to carry out functions, such as client services, consumer behavior surveys or similar activities relevant to business; it does not represent infringement of your data.

## Rules for the Protection of accounts and transactions

  * FX ProTrade system used to complete transactions safe for the protection of all trades and personal information at all times. Customer funds are quite far from any risk of loss or theft, you are the only person allowed to handle your finances.
  * Customer accounts with FX ProTrade completely separate from the company's accounts, you're the only person who has the right to handle them.
  * FX ProTrade dealing by firm fiscal policy, where it is a periodic review of the accounts at the hands of specialists.
  * All customer deposits and accounts covered with adequate liquidity.
  * FX ProTrade do not use Customer funds for any private or commercial purposes under any circumstances

## Latest technology for extra security

FX ProTrade trying to create a good position in the trading market, so fx ProTrade are keen on having the latest technology, which helps customers to achieve success, fx ProTrade has latest trading platforms and safest

  * The client has the ability to conduct transactions quickly and safely.
  * FX ProTrade use high-quality servers, to protect your transactions.

In the framework of this FX ProTrade always seeks to provide an all-new in the world of trading.

##  _Our goal is to maintain your money - because your success means our success_
